Chaz Lambrechtsen

Passionate Software Engineer

Location Sydney, NSW

Phone 0415 677 405

Email contact@caz-dev.com

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/chaz-lambrechtsen

Website <u>caz-dev.com</u>

GitHub github.com/CazDev



Summary

Motivated and high achieving individual studying Software Engineering (Honours) with 5+ years' experience developing personal projects, freelancing, win-forms, macros and more. Utilising programming languages such as C#, VB and Java. Please see my website and GitHub for more details.



Work History

2021 - Current **Software Engineer**

Interserv - Sydney, NSW

Developed software for government contracts including Australian Defence Force, Sydney trains and medical care application

2019 - 2021

IT Analyst & Engineer

Holman Webb - Sydney, NSW

- Developing .NET applications, win forms and Macros using C# and VB
- Deployed windows integrated Multi Factor Authentication across all offices
- Deployed enterprise AI cybersecurity software (<u>darktrace</u>) across network

2017 - 2018

Software Support Technician

KFC - Sydney, NSW

- Managed system-wide operating system and software deployments, as well as related software upgrade problems.
- Broke down and evaluated user problems, using test scripts, personal expertise and probing questions.

2016-2017

IT Technician

Animal Logic (Fox Studios) - Sydney, NSW

- Set up hardware and software in optimal configurations to meet network performance requirements.
- Established, repaired and optimized networks by installing wiring, cabling and devices.



Education

2018 - Current

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) in Software Engineering

Macquarie University - Sydney, NSW

- 71.6% WAM
- Coursework in IT, Software Design, Software Development (Java, React), Web Design, Web Development, Mathematics, Artificial Intelligence

2012 - 2018

Higher School Certificate

Concord High School - Sydney, NSW

- Completed Higher School Certificate
- Coursework in Software Development, Information Technology and Mathematics



Programming Languages

C#, Java, PHP, JavaScript

